Mm-hmm
I was freezing in the shadow, losing all the
light Drifting in the vacuum of a never-ending
night But the orbit kept on turning, the
mathematics held The ice upon the solar panel
slowly starts to melt I can see the star rising
over the horizon line
Everything is nominal, the telemetry is fine
Not too close to the atmospheric fire. Not too
far in the deep space wire. I found the perfect
circle, the habitable ring. I can feel the
warmth making the metal sing. I'm living. In the
Goldilocks Zone The perfect little orbit that I
call my own No more freezing in the dark No more
burning in the sun The calculations are
complete The heavy work is done I'm breathing in
the air I'm feeling so alive I found the perfect
distance to survive Right here in the
Goldilocks Zone
I used to think that gravity was gonna pull me
down, or I'd be lost in the empty where there
isn't any sound. But there's a narrow little
window where the water doesn't freeze, where
you can take the heavy space suit off and finally
catch a breeze. I'm planting down a flag in the
middle of the goal, a sanctuary story that is
waiting to be told. Too close to the atmospheric
fire. Not too far in the deep space wire. I found
the perfect circle, the habitable ring. I can
feel the warmth making the metal sing. I'm
living it. In the Goldilocks zone. The perfect
little orbit that I call my own. No more freezing
in the dark. No more burning in the sun. The
calculations are complete. The heavy work is
done. I'm breathing in the air. I'm feeling so
alive. I found the perfect distance to survive.
Right here in the Goldilocks zone No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
The temperature is holding The pressure is
exact The sanctuary is open And I'm never going
back
I'm living in the Goldilocks zone. The perfect
little orbit that I call my own. No more freezing
in the dark. No more burning in the sun.
Calculations are complete. The heavy work is
done. I'm breathing in the air. I'm feeling so
alive. I found the perfect distance to survive.
Right here in the Goldilocks zone.
The perfect distance
Right here in the ghost
Never going back